The Dead Center is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Billy Senese.
When a mysterious "John Doe" wakes up in a morgue and wanders into a psychiatric ward, a devoted doctor and curious medical examiner must
slowly uncover dark and sinister secrets about the man that reveal a more horrifying truth than they could have ever imagined.
Daniel Forrester, played by Shane Carruth.
Sarah Grey, played by Poorna Jagannathan.
John Doe, played by Jeremy Childs.
Edward Graham, played by Bill Feehely.
Travis, played by J. Thomas Bailey.
Parker, played by Quinn Cooke.
The Dead Center is a 2018 American horror mystery thriller film written
and directed by Billy Senese and starring Shane Carruth.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.